https://extendedlearning.ubc.ca/student-information/policies/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
UBC supports records management, information security and protection of privacy in accordance with:
UBC Policy #117, Records Management
UBC Policy #104, Acceptable Use and Security of UBC Electronic Information and Systems
the Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy Act R.S.B.C. 1996 c. 165, section 26(c).
For further information on Access and Privacy at UBC, please contact the Legal Counsel, Information and Privacy by email at access.and.privacy@ubc.ca.
Commitment to Privacy
Personal information provided on contact, subscription or registration forms is collected pursuant to section 26(c) of the Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy Act (FIPPA), RSBC 1996, c.165, as amended. The information will be used for the purposes of: answering inquiries; admission; registration; academic progress; notification of future courses; and operating other UBC-related programs. UBC collects, uses, retains and discloses information in accordance with FIPPA. UBC may share and disclose personal information within the University to carry out its mandate and operations. Information, in aggregate form only, may also be used for research purposes and statistics.
Should you have any questions about the collection of information, please contact the Managing Director, Student Engagement and Marketing, UBC Extended Learning, 410-5950 University Boulevard, Vancouver, BC, V6T 1Z3.
Updating Your Student Registration Profile
At any time you can update your profile in UBC Extended Learning’s student registration system to let us know if you no longer wish to receive emails, phone calls, and/or mailings from UBC Extended Learning. To indicate how you would like us to communicate with you, please log into the system and click on your name in the upper right, select > Edit Profile. To retire your record please call +1.604.822.1444.
Updating Your Email Subscription Preferences
If at any time you wish to change your preferences or be removed from our subscription lists, click the "Update Your Preferences" or "Unsubscribe" links found at the bottom of each email.
Website Information and Online Advertising
We may work with third parties using cookies, web beacons, and similar technologies to collect or receive non-personal information in aggregate and use that information to provide measurement services and targeted ads. This information is kept indefinitely. This helps us promote our website (and UBC) to those who have already shown an interest in UBC.
You can opt out of this collection and use of information for ad targeting at any time: Understanding Online Advertising. If you have opted-out of web tracking through your internet browser we will not track your visit.
If you have any questions about how your information is collected in relation to the website or online advertising , please contact our Legal Counsel, Information and Privacy.
See also UBC Extended Learning Admissions, Refund and Cancellation, and Code of Conduct Policies.
FAQs: CORONAVIRUS and ExL Programs
How to Register
About Our Credentials
About Online Learning
PoliciesRefund Policy
Privacy Policy
Code of Conduct and Appeals
Tuition Tax Receipts
Request Forms
Frequently Asked Questions
Useful Links for Lifelong Learners
Agents
Product names used throughout this website are trademarks or registered trademarks of their respective holders.
UBC Copyright Website
Main menuHome
Courses and Programs
Student InformationFAQs: CORONAVIRUS and ExL Programs
How to Register
About Our Credentials
About Online Learning
Policies
Warning for Internet Explorer Users
We have detected that you are using an older version of Internet Explorer. While we have made every effort to accommodate all users, portions of our website may not display or function properly with your current browser. We suggest you upgrade to another browser such as IE10+, Chrome, or Firefox.
